John W. Warner papers MSS 10191
University of Virginia, Special Collections Dept.
- John Warner papers (-by accession), 1970-2007; MSS 10191_by; 713 Cubic Feet Cubic foot boxes; This collection consists of 712 cubic foot boxes.
  - Videotapes, 9/22/1978-12/31/2004 (Box 538)
    001: "Senator", Friends of John Warner #139, St. Mary's Associates, 10/31/1996 [VHS]; 695: 9/11 Commission, Tapes 1 & 2, 3/24/2004 [2 VHS]; 686: Senate Armed Services Committee, David Kay Hearing; Nominations Hearing, 1/28/2004 [VHS]; 696 & 697: 9/11 Commission Day 1, Tapes 1 & 2, 3/23/2004 [2 VHS]; 004: Spot Compilation Reel, Mark Warner for U.S. Senate 1996, Stevens Reed Curcio & Company [VHS]; 692: Senator John Warner and Senator Hollings Codel, Iraq Footage, 4/16/2004 [BetaCam]; 009: "For the Kids" and "Meet Priscilla", Greg Stevens & Company, 7/27/1995 and 8/4/1995 [VHS]; 033: "It's Miller Time", Friends of John Warner, Greg Stevens & Company, 6/5/1995 [VHS]; 010 & 034: "Honor - Revised", Friends of John Warner, Greg Stevens & Company, 5/21/1996 [2 VHS]; 690 & 691: "Liberia: America's Step Child", 2/4/2004 [2 VHS]; 693: Untitled VHS; 029: Political Spot Compilation Reel, Greg Stevens & Company, 12/12/1994 [VHS]; 688: Oprah Tape, Air Force Academy, 12/8/2003 [VHS]; 158: WJLA-TV, Virginia Senate Race, Warner vs. Miller, New Edit Copy, 9/22/1978 (aired 9/23/1978) [U-Matic]; 689: Senate Armed Services Committee, 2/10/2003 [VHS]; 011: Demo Reel, Ringe Media, Inc., 1995 [VHS]; 030: Todd M. Hahn Original Music Composition, Broadcast/Corporate, Henninger Digital Audio [VHS]; 028: "Quick" and "What We Promised", Greg Stevens & Company, 12/1/1995 [VHS]; 687: Floor Statement, 3/31/2004 [VHS]; 157: C-Span, Call-in with Senator John Warner, 3/18/1985 [U-Matic]; 024: Select Spots, Gilmore '97, St. Mary's Associates, 8/21/1997 [VHS]; 002, 025 & 031: "Honor", Friends of John Warner, Greg Stevens & Company, 5/8/1996 [3 VHS]; 357: Sabato Class [8mm video tape]
  - Videotapes, 1/1/1982-12/31/2000 (Box 539)
    377: "Choosing Sides: I Remember Vietnam, The War At Home", WinStar Home Entertainment, 1998 [VHS]; 507: "Portraits of America - Virginia", 1983 [VHS]; 368: CNN, Pentagon Hearing, 10/11/2000 [VHS]; 379: "For the Kids" and "Meet Priscilla", Greg Stevens & Company, 7/27/1995 and 8/4/1995 [VHS]; 383: Senator John Warner Press Conference, Stealth, 9/16/1997 [BetaCam]; Senator John Warner Speech - Ferrum College Commencement, 5/6/1990 [empty VHS case]; 516: 09307 [1 inch Videotape on Reel]; 367: Nightline, "Medi-Scare", 12/12/1995 [VHS]; 363: Anthrax Statement, 10/16/2001 [BetaCam]; 362: Larry King Live, Mideast/USS Cole, 10/12/2000 [VHS]; 378: Today, Segment re: North, 7/28/1994 [VHS]; 520: Senator John Warner #298, 3/9/1982 [U-Matic]; 369: Spring Commencement 2000, Senator John Warner, Virginia Tech [VHS]; 522: U.S. Senator John W. Warner (R-Va.) and Former U.S. Senator George McGovern (D-SD) Debate the Nuclear Freeze at the University of Pennsylvania Public Forum "Toward Preventing Nuclear War", Irvine Auditorium, 3/30/1983 [1 Inch Videotape on Reel]; 415: Senator John Warner Press Conference, 6/14/2001 [BetaCam]; 316: Channel 9, with Senator John Warner at ATOKA [VHS]; 521: Yorktown CG48 Launching, 4/16/1984 [U-Matic-S]; 523: Yorktown CG 48 Ceremony, 4/16/1983 [U-Matic]; 446: WTTG - Washington, D.C., "Inaugural Opening Ceremonies" [Beta]; 519: Senator John Warner #459, 4/6/1982 [U-Matic]
  - Audio Recordings, 1/1/1978-12/31/1996 (Box 540)
    468: John Warner Promos by G.W. Whitehurst, 10/12/1978 [audiocassette]; 455: Shad Planking, Waverly, Virginia, 4/18/1979 [audiocassette]; 493: Senator Warner/Hammett [audiocassette]; 227: Erkilitian FR (Arlington), 3/20/1996; Fairfax County Convention (Miscellaneous) [audiocassette]; 477: Town Meeting Kennedy Center, Braden & Buchannan [audiocassette]; 230: Warner, 7/4/1995 [audiocassette]; 448: Town Meeting Kennedy Center; National Public Radio, Helen Whelean Defense Spending, 1/4/1982 [audiocassette]; 464: Senator Jackson on Face the Nation, 2/20 [audiocassette]; 504: Hampton Roads Maritime Association, Norfolk, Virginia, 5/6/1980 [audiocassette]; 255-258, 434-435, 437, 440, 443, 454, 473, 474, 485, & 490: 14 Untitled audiocassettes; 237: Generic General Assembly Endorsement, Friends of John Warner, 1995 [audiocassette]; 505: Judge Sheffield Group, Dirksen Building, 5/9/1980 [audiocassette]; 344: Don Baker's VCU Class, 4/18 [audiocassette]; 452: Senator John Warner, Dutch Treat Luncheon, Richmond, Virginia, 1/6/1980 [audiocassette]; 510: U.S. Senator John W. Warner (R-Va.) and Former U.S. Senator George McGovern (D-SD) Debate the Nuclear Freeze at the University of Pennsylvania Public Forum "Toward Preventing Nuclear War", Irvine Auditorium, 3/30/1983 [reel to reel]; 355: RPV, 5/18/1989 [audiocassette]; 513: Audio Track of Video [reel to reel]; 499: Lincoln Day Dinner, Columbus, Ohio, 2/15/1980; Columbus Press Conference [audiocassette]; 487: Senator John Warner New Availability, re: Judgeships, Alexandria Courthouse, 4/13/1981 [audiocassette]; 486 & 500: Wayne/Senator John Warner Luncheon, Capitol Hill, 3/6/1980 [2 audiocassettes]; 226: Senator John Warner Radio Conference, 3/8/1996 [audiocassette]; 466: Dick Allen, Senator John Warner Et al Foreign Press Briefing, 6/20 [audiocassette]; 353: Senator John Warner 1990 Radio; Nunn/Senator John Warner re: Tower, 2/6/1989; CBS [audiocassette]; 217: NPR and Internet Launch, 4/9/1996 [audiocassette]; 480 & 484: Heinz Seminar, Tapes 2 & 3 [2 audiocassettes]; 459: Conference of Christians and Jews, Hampton, Virginia, 3/1/1979 [audiocassette]; 462: Armed Services, DoD Authorization, 1/30 [audiocassette]; 342: Richmond Trip, 3/30 [audiocassette]; 225: Herrico and Fairfax GOP Mass Meetings/Convention, 3/23/1996 [audiocassette]; 359: The BQ Show 3:00 - 4:00 P.M., Oliver North, 9/19/1994 [audiocassette]; 441: Senator John Warner, Republican State Convention, Richmond, 1993 [audiocassette]; 220: Fox 5 and NYT 6/6/1996 and 6/17/1996 [audiocassette]; 343: "The Dalton Gang Working Together", Paramel Productions [audiocassette]; 231: Miller and Pro-Family Press Conference, 3/12/1996 [audiocassette]; 450: MBS, Reporters Roundup, Guest Senator John Warner, 9/21/1980 [audiocassette]; Bob Tata/Delegate, "Senator John Warner Endorse", 1991 [audiocassette]; 252: FEC Conference, 5/6/1996; Bork Spot, 5/9/1996 [audiocassette]; 213: Senator John Warner, Daily Press Ed. Board, 5/24/1996 [audiocassette]; 246: Charles Hawkins Endorsement, Friends of John Warner, Greg Stevens & Company, 9/21/1995 [audiocassette]; 491: News Availability, Charlottesville, 4/17 [audiocassette]; 501: Edward Roeder Interview, Senator John Warner Office, 3/13/1980 [audiocassette]; 242-244: "Who's Jim Miller", "Why", and "Avoided", Friends of John Warner, Greg Stevens & Company, 5/21/1996 [3 audiocassettes]; 445: Senator John Warner at AP Dinner, Richmond, "Raw Meat", 2/3/1995 [audiocassette]; 463: Richmond Press Conference, 4/14 [audiocassette]; 471: "The Senators", Senator John Warner, 3 Shows [audiocassette]; 264: Generic General Assembly Endorsement, Friends of John Warner, Greg Stevens & Company, Master Tape, 9/21/1995 [DAT]; 449: Fundraising Dinner, Richmond, 3/7/1981; Senator John Warner on Charlie Huddle, 3/2/1983 [audiocassette]; 518: Plenary Session, MIT Law Afternoon Session, 1/13/1977; SALT#3, RICH, 6/12/1979 [reel to reel]; 492: Armed Forces Staff College, Norfolk, Virginia, 1/18/1980 [audiocassette]; 497: Senator John Warner, U.S. Tobacco Employees, Richmond, Virginia, 2/12/1980 [audiocassette]; 482: News Conference - ACE 3000, 1980 Richlands Coal Show, Richlands, Virginia, 9/11/1980 [audiocassette]; 223: Bristol/Harrisonburg 2/23; Richmond/Alexandria/Norfolk, 2/22 [audiocassette]; 251: Miller, NRA Richmond, 5/8/1996 [audiocassette]; 356: Bush Dinner, 3/8/1990 [audiocassette]; 224: Miller/Senator John Warner Fairfax City Joint Appearance, 3/18 [audiocassette]; 221: 6/6/1996 - 6/8/1996 [audiocassette]; 436: "An American Framework: Framing the Issues", Pete du Pont, GOPAC, 10/1995 [audiocassette]; 249: WLVA AM590, Jim Miller Breakfast and Talk Interview: Primary Votes, Debates, Abortion Notification, 3/15/1996 [audiocassette]; 442: WAMU, Miller PAC, 10/23/1995 [audiocassette]; 467: Laird [audiocassette]; 563: CVN 77 Naming Ceremony [CR-RW]; 502: Virginia Trial Lawyers Association, Williamsburg, Virginia, 3/22/1980 [audiocassette]; 472: Meet the Member, Senator John Warner, 1/19/1979 [audiocassette]; 496: 6th District Economic Conference, Natural Bridge, Virginia, 2/11/1980 [audiocassette]; 479: Saratoga Hearing [audiocassette]; 461: Meg Rosenfeld Interview/WP [audiocassette]; 453: Virginia Independent Telephone Association, Hot Springs, Virginia, 10/19/1979; Brown Briefing [audiocassette]; 240 & 241: "Welfare", "Budget" and "General Assembly", Friends of John Warner, Greg Stevens & Company [2 audiocassettes]; 239: "Welfare", "Budget", "General Assembly", Friends of John Warner, Greg Stevens & Company, 10/5/1995 [audiocassette]; 234: Mike Warner [audiocassette]; 346: George Allen, Breakfast, Senator John Warner, Representative Newt Gingrich and George Allen, Belle Haven Country Club, Alexandria, Virginia, 9/29/1993 [audiocassette]; 229: Ted Byrd Interview, 9/16/1995 [audiocassette]; 481: Prayer Service, 4/3/1981 [audiocassette]; 517: Recorded?; SALT Reel #2, RICH., 6/12/1979 [reel to reel]; 347: Senator John Warner PSA, "Academy Day 1992" [audiocassette]; 438-439: Regardie's Profile with William Saletan, Tapes 1 & 2 [2 audiocassettes]; 263: WBZS, Jerry Springer, Mark Warner, 4/18 [audiocassette]; 218: WINA/WOMZ/WKAV, Senator John Warner Talk-Back with Bob Gibson, 6/4/1996 [audiocassette]; 341: "History and Leadership", GOPAC Charter Meeting 4/24 to 4/25, Newt Gingrich and Lady Margaret Thatcher, 5/1994 [audiocassette]; 235: Richmond, Senator John Warner Press Conference on Litigation, 3/25/1996 [audiocassette]; 458: National Tour Brokers Association, Orlando, Florida, 1/10/1980 [audiocassette]; 253 & 254: Salem, Blacksburg, Wepers Cave, and Cville, 5/30 to 6/1 [2 audiocassettes]; 506: Banquet, Virginia Republican State Convention, Richmond, Virginia, 6/6/1980 [audiocassette]; 232: Edinburg, 2/24/1996 [audiocassette]; 349: Announcement Tour, 2/5/1990 [audiocassette]; 470: Senator John Warner, Course 120, Graduation Exercise AFSC Class 66, 1/18/1980 [audiocassette]; 245: "Support" w/o Disclaimer, Friends of John Warner, Greg Stevens & Company, 10/30/1995 [audiocassette]; 444: Lloyd Grove re: BW [audiocassette]; 498: CNN Press Conference; Lincoln Day Dinner, Cincinnati, Ohio, 2/14/1980 [audiocassette]; 345: Senator John Warner Farm PSA [audiocassette]; 236: Miller Ad Response Press Conference, 5/16/1996 [audiocassette]; 248: Lexington - Wtc, 3/1/1996 & 3/2/1996 [audiocassette]; 456: Admiral Rickover [audiocassette]; 483: Huntsville, Alabama; Alabama Press Conference [audiocassette]; 250: Bob Gibson, 4/10/1996 [audiocassette]; 460: Senator John Warner - Jerry Brown, 4/13/1979; Bill Miller [audiocassette]; 214: WNIS, Dr. Moller, 6/11/1996 [audiocassette]; 352: Sam Donaldson, 6/22/1992; Peter Harding, 1/21/1992 [audiocassette]; 233: Lynchburg/Danville, 2/24/1996 [audiocassette]; 358: Governor Allen's Congress Roundtable, AM, Senator John Warner, BC, 3/29/1994 [audiocassette]; 215: Dole Endorsement, 5/4/1996 [audiocassette]; 354: Painting Notes from Arnett [audiocassette]; 238: WRVA Radio, Jim Miller with Lou Dean, 6/6/1996 [audiocassette]; 350: Lloyd Grove, 12/14/1989 [audiocassette]; 512: Byrd, Tape #2 [reel to reel]; 451: Senator John Warner, Dutch Treat Luncheon, Norfolk, Virginia, 1/18/1980 [audiocassette]; Gannett, CIA, 11/26/1991 [audiocassette]; 494: Chamber of Commerce Dinner, Radford, Virginia, 2/11/1980 [audiocassette]; 216: Peter Hardin, 5/26/1996 [audiocassette]; 475: Senator John Warner, Coleman Headquarters Opening, 9/5/1981; Battle of the Virginia Capes, Virginia Beach [audiocassette]; 469: WHK and Jim Clarke WJLA; WHK and WRVA Radio [audiocassette]; 259-262: 4 Untitled Microcassettes; 228: Peter Baker, 4/25/1996 [audiocassette]; 247: Senator John Warner Interviews with Jim Perry and Peter Hardin, 4/23/1996 [audiocassette]; 351: Lloyd Grove, 8/11/1989 [audiocassette]; 503: Navy Federal Credit Union, Vienna, Virginia, 3/24/1980 [audiocassette]; 478: Mark Shields, Business and Government Relations Council, Winsby, 9/19/1980 [audiocassette]; 488: Memphis, 10/28; 6 Ads, Alabama & Burton Lunch [audiocassette]; 360: Peter Hardin, TTD; Cokie Roberts, CNN; Laurie Kellman, TWT; Dave McConnell, TOP; Jan Smith, Fox [audiocassette]; 219: Barrett-Times/Welsh, USA Today, 5/2/1996 [audiocassette]; 457: Interviews: Henry Eason, Nation's Business; Nancy King, Virginia Network; Jim Canan, Business Week, 2/16/1983 [audiocassette]; 495: Chamber of Commerce Dinner, Radford, Virginia, 2/11/1980; Senator John Warner/Hammett [audiocassette]; 476: CSNY, Zevon [audiocassette]; 509, 514 & 515: 3 Untitled Reel to Reel; 489: Today, 10/28/1981 [audiocassette]; 447 & 465: WNIS, Senator John Warner/Gordon Hammett, Sides 1-4, 10/25/1979 [2 audiocassettes]; 348: Pledge, Master, 3/3/1990 [audiocassette]; 222: Senator John Warner/Senator Bond Fundraiser, 4/30/1996 [audiocassette]; 511: Keynote Address, 1/13/1977; SALT Reel #1, RICH., 6/12/1979 [reel to reel]
  - Photographs, 1/1/1992-12/31/2000 (Box 541)
    Press [envelope]; 2 Untitled Envelopes; Outdate Senator John Warner Formal Black and White Portrait [box]; 2 Untitled Accordion Folders; Senator John Warner Formal Color and Black and White Portraits [box]; Senator John Warner and Martha Washington at Mount Vernon Wine Festival [envelope]; Armed Services "Change of Command" pictures [envelope]; Photo Studio SD-685 [envelope]; The White House [envelope]
  - Photographs, 1/1/1982-12/31/1992 (Box 542)
    Eastern Europe, Berlin Wall, 1989 [envelope]; 1983; Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1992; 1982; Photographs, 1990; 2 Untitled Accordion Folders
  - Campaign Materials, 1/1/1995-12/31/2005 (Box 543)
    Campaign, 1995-2000 [accordion folder]; Untitled Accordion Folder; Political 1988, Bork; Today; 1995 Constitutional Right to Primary Election [accordion folder]; 1998 Congressional [accordion folder]; Senator John Warner 2002: Campaign Volunteers; 1998 Campaign; Senator John Warner 2002: Campaign/Casework; Lawsuit; Michael Wilding [accordion folder]; Senator John Warner 2002 [accordion folder]; Mark Warner [accordion folder]; Mark Warner, 2001
  - Campaign Materials, 1/1/1993-12/31/2002 (Box 544)
    "Achievable Dream", Metro Video Productions, 7/16/1997 [VHS]; U.S. Senate Memos; 1996 Senate Race, Senator John Warner Items; Senator John Warner v. Miller; Warner Calendars, 1995-1996 [envelopes]; Transportation Builder, ARTBA, 5/2000 [magazine]; Untitled Presentation Folder: Rules Committee, 1994; "Choosing Sides: I Remember Vietnam, Fields of Fire", Non Fiction Films, 1998 [VHS]; 2 Untitled Presentation Folders: Lyndon LaRouche, 1994; 2 Untitled Folders: Senator Packwood; Election Law; Untitled Presentation Folder: 1998 Senate Campaign; Speeches and Statements; Press Releases; Nancy Spannaus; VDDA Navy Housing Event, Henninger, Richmond, 4/1998 [VHS]; Loose Papers: Press Releases; Campaign Notes; Changing the Name of the Library of Congress, 1993-1998; Welcome to Alexandria; NATO; Crook, G. Gail; Warner Donor Volunteer Lists [envelopes]; "Defeat Ollie North, That Son-of-a-Bush", 1994 [booklet] (2 copies); Jacob Hornberger, 2002 Campaign; Breast Cancer Notes, Draft Speech [presentation folder]
  - Personnel Recommendations, K - S (Dariene Steeves), 1/1/2002-12/31/2005 (Box 545)
    87 Folders, Kasten, Aleyda to Sugar, Ron
  - Appropriations: Commerce, Justice, Science, and Related Agencies and Labor, Health and Human Services, Education, and Related Agencies (Chris Yianilos), 1/1/2004-12/31/2005 (Box 546)
    FY 2005 Labor HHS: New Beginnings SW Virginia; CJS 2005: William & Mary (Court 21); CJS 2005: Lonesome Pine; Labor HHS 2005: Carilion Health; CJS 2005: Hampton Alert; CJS 2005: 0 - 3 (Zero to Three); CJS 2005: Achievable Dream; FY 2005 Labor: Virginia Beach; Berryville Citizens Association; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Eastern Virginia Medical School; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Jamestown Commission; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Jeremiah Project; FY 2005 Labor HHS: NORC Richmond; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Monster Gat Sol; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Jewish Family Services of Tidewater; Social Security Title IV-C Funds; FY 2005 Labor: Philip Theodosiou; FY 2005 Labor HHS: New Beginnings; FY 2005 Labor: University of Virginia - Youth Leadership Initiative; CJS 2005: Suffolk; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Our Health, Russ Potts; Fairfax City and Title I Allocation; FY 2005 Labor: Virginia Military Institute; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Culpepper Dental; CJS 2005: Cops Appropriation VCPI; FY 2005 Labor: St. John Baptist in the Woods; FY 2005 Labor: University of Appalachia; Labor HHS 2005: Christopher Newport; FY 2005 Labor: William & Mary; Labor HHS 2005: Alliance for Consumer Education; Labor HHS 2005: Samples; FY 2005 Labor: Riverside; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Children's Hospital of the King's Daughters; CJS 2005: ATF Request; Labor HHS 2005: Bon Secours; FY 2005 Labor: Virginia Museum of Fine Arts; FY 2005 Labor: Wolf Trap; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Northern Virginia Hospital Alliance (NVHA); CJS 2005: Alexandria; FY 2005 Labor HHS: INOVA - Clark Moore; CJS 2005: CHKD (Children's Hospital of the King's Daughters); CJS 2005: Center for Criminal Justice Tech (Mitretek); Labor HHS 2005: Arl Free Clinic; FY 2005 Labor: Virginia Living Museum; FY 2005 Labor HHS: City of Portsmouth; Labor HHS 2005: Bellmont; FY 2005 Labor HHS: James Madison University; FY 2005 Labor: Virginia Community College System; FY 2005 Labor: Patient Services; Labor HHS 2005: Black Lung; CJS 2005: Chesapeake; Boy Scouts of America; FY 2005 Labor: Virginia High School League; Labor HHS 2005: Achievable Dream; CJS 2005: Appropriations Information (C.J.S.); FY 2005 Labor: Woodrow Wilson (Presidential Library); FY 2005 Labor: Virginia Osteopathic; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Eastern Mennonite University; Labor HHS 2005: American Military Spouse Foundation (AMSEF); FY 2005 Labor HHS: George Mason University; CJS 2005: Shenandoah; FY 2005 Labor HHS: First Freedom; FY 2005 Labor: Regent; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Experience Works; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Institute for Advanced Learning, Danville; FY 2005 Labor HHS: Lynch - Academy of Fine Arts; FY 2005 Labor: Parents Anonymous; FY 2005 Labor: O. Winston Link Museum; Labor HHS 2005: Center for Mental Health Services; Labor HHS 2005: America on the Move; FY 2005 Labor HHS: National Federation of the Blind; FY 2005 Labor: Project Access; FY 2005 Labor: Patient Advocate Foundation (PAF)
  - Nominations, Inaugural Ceremony, and Northern Virginia Women's Conference, 1/1/1989-12/31/2001 (Box 547)
    Colin L. Powell, General USA, Chairman, Joint Chiefs of Staff [accordion folder]; Powell, Colin USA/JCS Nomination File/2nd Term [accordion folder]; Northern Virginia Women's Conference, 1990 [accordion folder]; Colonel James J. Steele, USA Nomination File; David Addington to Be DoD General Counsel; Hemingway, Col. Thomas L. USAF, Promotion File; Inaugural, 2001; Wiss, Robert E., Court of Military Appeals Nomination; Studeman, William O. to Be Deputy Director CIA; Gierke, Herman F., Court of Military Appeals Nomination; Crawford, Susan, Court Military Appeals Nomination
  - Military and Defense Issues (Sam/Cord Sterling), 1/1/1999-12/31/2001 (Box 548)
    VA-HUD Appropriations Bill (Passed 9/24) [accordion folder]; FY 2000 Defense Appropriations/Foreign Operations Appropriations, 6/30 [accordion folder]; Commerce - Justice - State Appropriations [accordion folder]; FY 2001 Defense Appropriations; FY 2000 National Defense Authorization (Amendments, C.R.'s, Dear Colleagues) [accordion folder]; Women on Submarines [accordion folder]; Military Construction Appropriations/State Department Reauthorization, 6/22 [accordion folder]
  - Executive Branch Nominee Information and Governmental Affairs Materials (John Frierson), 1/1/2005-12/31/2006 (Box 549)
    Nomination: Springer, Hearing 5/18/2005 [binder]; Portman OMB Nomination 109th, 5/17/2006 [presentation folder]; Staunton/Roanoke Trip, 8/8 - 8/9/2005 [binder]; Nomination: Bilbray, Marshall, Blair, Hearing 11/14/2006 [binder]; Nomination: Doan, Hearing 5/22/2006 [binder]; Nomination: Combs, Hearing 5/25/2005 [binder]; Governors of USPS Confirmation Hearing, 6/29/2006 [presentation folder]; Susan Dudley OMB Nomination [accordion folder]; Nomination: Paulison, Hearing 5/24/2006 [binder]; Nomination: McMillin, Hearing 7/13/2006 [binder]; Business Meeting, 6/22/2005 [binder]; Nomination: Portman, Hearing 5/17/2006 [binder]; 5 Steno Pads, Floor Notes 2005-2006
  - Armed Services Committee, 1/1/1986-12/31/1992 (Box 550)
    The Almanac of Seapower, Navy League of the United States, 1989 & 1992 [2 books]; Unauthorized Appropriations - History; Committee Business - Trip Reports; Civil Service [accordion folder]; Committee Inquiries - Stephen Breyer; Committee Inquiries - National Security Strategy [accordion folder]; Military Justice - Court Structure Issues; Committee Business - Procedures; Air Force Magazine, 1992 US Air Force Almanac, Air Force Association; Air Force Magazine, 1991 USAF Almanac/Operation Desert Storm; Civil Service: War Powers; Committee Business - Security
  - Military and Defense Issues (Sam/Cord Sterling), 1/1/1993-10/1/2002 (Box 551)
    Mary Baldwin; Mothball Fleet (3 folders); MSMC Heritage Fund (U.S. Marine Corps); George Washington University; Swanson Molt; Box with 43 3.5" Disks of Backup Files, Press Releases, Briefing Materials, Trip Files, and Photographs, 1993-2001; Travel; Strategic Insights; Veterans, Retirees, and Assorted Associations; NASCAR; James Madison; TRAC; Thank Yous; Ship Wreck Allocation; Ship Repair
  - Daily Schedules and Accepted Invitations, 3/1/1984-10/31/1984 (Box 552)
    U.S. Senate Stationery; Accepted Scheduling Items [accordion folder]; Scheduling Files (8 folders)
  - Military and Defense Issues (Sam/Cord Sterling), 1/1/1999-12/31/2002 (Box 553)
    William and Mary; University of Virginia; V-22 Info Papers; Roanoke/Virginia Tech, 5/12/2000 - 5/13/2000; University of Virginia, USAID; WorldSpace [presentation folder]; August Recess District Work Period 2002 (2 copies); Trip File: Virginia Tech/Blacksburg/Dublin, 8/2/1999 (2 folders); World Space (?); Loose Papers: Press Clippings and Newspapers, 2001-2002; C. Warner; Judy/Carter (?); Virginia Tech; Analysis Converting SSBNS to SSGNS; Conversations with America 2000 (2 copies, each in 3 folders); Susan; Dulles High Tech Tour, 7/26/1999 (2 copies); Virginia Danville
  - Military and Defense Issues, 1/1/1997-12/31/2001 (Box 554)
    FY 2002 NDAA: Passed Floor Amendments; FY 2002 NDAA: House Requested Conference Support; 9/11/2001 [accordion folder]; FY 2002 NDAA: Supplemental Appropriations; Missile Defense [accordion folder]; FY 2002 Budget [accordion folder]; Submarine Centennial; FY 2002 NDAA: National Defense Features Program; Killed in Action, Boise de Hattonville, Hattonville, France, 9 November, 1944 Subject: Delayed Memorial Affairs Crash Site - Search and Recovery and Application for Possible French Decorations [binder]; FY 2002 NDAA [accordion folder]; 9/11/2001: Foreign Expressions of Support; 9/11/2001: Casualty Lists; FY 2002 NDAA: Demilitarization of Military Equipment; FY 2002 NDAA: Pending Floor Amendments; FY 2002 NDAA: Priorities; Naval Reactors Commemorative; FY 2002 NDAA: HASC Outsourcing Issues; Old Letters; Turnover [empty accordion folder]; FY 2002 NDAA: Challenge Program; FY 2002 NDAA: Health Information Assurance; Homeland Defense [accordion folder]; FY 2002 NDAA: Conference Issues
  - Energy, Transportation, Environment, and Public Works (Conrad Schatte), 1/1/2000-12/31/2003 (Box 555)